Guide to the William Shockley Papers SC0222
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-198
  - Correspondence
    - correspondence, miscellaneous, 1957-1998
      - Incoming Correspondence
        - Incoming Correspondence- DP Moynihan (Shockley CCed), 1967 Apr 2 (Box 121, Folder 14)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Mrs. Gail Morris, 1967 Oct 11 (Box 121, Folder 15)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Richard Robert, 1969 Apr 23 (Box 121, Folder 16)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Joseph Christian, 1967 Sep 18 (Box 121, Folder 17)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc., 1970-1972 (Box 121, Folder 21)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Richard Hayden, 1971 Dec 6 (Box 121, Folder 25)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Unknown (name cut out), 1969 Jul 14 (Box 121, Folder 27)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Charles Gubser (US Congress), 1972 Jan 4 (Box 121, Folder 29)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Phan, Mary re Perkins & Vernon Scott, 1972 Mar (Box 121, Folder 32)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Donald Jensen, 1968 Aug 20 (Box 121, Folder 37)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Kenneth A. Lehner, 1970 Feb-Apr (Box 121, Folder 39)
        - Incoming Correspondence - RT Osborne, 1970 Jun 24 (Box 121, Folder 41)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Eugeneics Fans (reprints), 1972 Feb (Box 121, Folder 42)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Roger L. Mosher (reprints), 1970 Jul 13 (Box 121, Folder 44)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Military & Eugeneics, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 48)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc., 1972 (Box 121, Folder 49)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Stanford Republican Party & Pat Reynolds, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 57)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Dr. Daniel Carlson, 1991 Jun 24 (Box 123, Folder 1)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Stephan A. Cisler, 1990 May 14 (Box 123, Folder 2)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Nathen Brody, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 4)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Helmuth Nyborg, 1987 Sep 4 (Box 123, Folder 5)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Hiram Caton, 1987 Oct 5 (Box 123, Folder 6)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Ronald Fletcher, 1987 Aug 18 (Box 123, Folder 7)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Arthur Jensen, 1989 Jun (Box 123, Folder 9)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Robert Caucro MD, 1981 Jun 25 (Box 123, Folder 11)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Robert McConnell, 1989 Mar 10 (Box 123, Folder 15)
        - Incoming Correspondence - HMB, 1989 Aug 7 (Box 123, Folder 44)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Robert E. Kuttner, 1971 Jul (Box 122, Folder 18)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Guy D. Boston, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 33)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Sylvia Crutchfield, 1974 Dec 11 (Box 122, Folder 39)
        - Incoming Correspondence - H. Gary Knight, 1976 Aug 16 (Box 124, Folder 5)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Lowell Wood, 1976 Aug 9-17 (Box 124, Folder 7)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Eb Rechtin, 1976 Aug 19 (Box 124, Folder 9)
        - Incoming Correspondence - David A. Bufalini, 1976 Feb 11 (Box 124, Folder 15)
        - X=WS - Kad Draft of "Cervase Letter"/ Incoming Correspondence - John Cervase, 1974 Apr (Box 124, Folder 45)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Natheniel D.M. Hirsch, 1972-1974 (Box 124, Folder 47)
        - Incoming Correspondence re. W. Shockley, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 48)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Nippon Hoso Kyokai Broadcasting (Box 125, Folder 5)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Wisconsin Society of Science Teachers, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 10)
        - Incoming Corrspondence - Robert A Lee (South Africa Made Simple), 1987 Jul 31 (Box 129, Folder 23)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Karen M. Bloom, 1987 May 22 (Box 130, Folder 18)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Harvard University, 1968 Dec 20 (Box 137, Folder 6)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Equations & Theories, 1968 Jan-May (Box 137, Folder 13)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Princeton University, 1997 Nov (Box 138, Folder 13)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Gerald R. Ford, 1976 May 18 (Box 138, Folder 22)
        - Incoming Correspondence - FN Jones Jr., 1976 Dec 21 (Box 138, Folder 26)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc. re Eugeneics, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 30)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Charles Clayton, 1973 Dec 12 (Box 138, Folder 34)
        - Incoming Correspondence - John Norman Warnock, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 36)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc. (reprints), 1973 (Box 138, Folder 37)
        - Incoming Correspondence (reprint) - Lee B. Jamison, 1974 Jan 3 (Box 138, Folder 41)
        - Incoming Correspondence - James J Diehl, 1973 Dec 27 (Box 138, Folder 42)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Eugeneics, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 43)
        - Incoming Correspondence - David Schulson, 1976 Jun (Box 138, Folder 45)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Audrey Shuey, 1974 Jan 7 (Box 138, Folder 49)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc. re FREED & Eugeneics, 1973-1974 (Box 138, Folder 50)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Glen Pullan, 1974 Jan 4 (Box 138, Folder 51)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Peter A. Bookman, 1976 Nov (Box 138, Folder 55)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Eugeneics, 1976 Aug-Nov (Box 138, Folder 56)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Fredrick Smith (reprint), 1976 Oct 11 (Box 138, Folder 58)
        - Incoming Correspondence (reprint) - Dianne Levy, 1976 Oct 7 (Box 138, Folder 60)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Lorraine Friedman, 1976 Dec 14 (Box 138, Folder 63)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Toshimistu Musha (reprint), 1976 Dec 11 (Box 138, Folder 64)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Charles R. Stone (reprint), 1973 May 21 (Box 138, Folder 65)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Abert Bridges (reprint), 1973 (Box 138, Folder 66)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Charles Stein (reprint), 1973 May 29 (Box 138, Folder 68)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc. (reprint), 1973 (Box 138, Folder 69)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc. (reprint), 1973-1974 (Box 138, Folder 72)
          Scribbles & notes on the correspondence and some had the (+) as on some of the other previous correspondences.
        - Incoming Correspondence - Billie Josline (reprint), 1973 Jun (Box 138, Folder 73)
        - Incoming Correspondence - John Linvill re Sabbatical, 1973 Jul 5 (Box 138, Folder 74)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Political, 1973 Aug (Box 138, Folder 78)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Xeroxed Correspondence (reprint), 1973 Aug (Box 138, Folder 79)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Paul Kern & Articles, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 80)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Patricia Loud re. Paul Hopper & Mr. Hine, 1973 May 18 (Box 138, Folder 81)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Cyirl Darlington, 1973 May-Jun (Box 138, Folder 83)
        - Incoming Correspondence - To Emmy & William (reprints), 1973-1976 (Box 138, Folder 85)
        - Incoming Correspondence - FJ van Empel & JA Poulis, 1973 May 4 (Box 139, Folder 2)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Sandra White, 1973 May 21 (Box 139, Folder 5)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Robert LeFevre, 1973 Apr 30 (Box 139, Folder 6)
        - Incoming Correspondence - John Millington, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 7)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Misc., 1973 (Box 139, Folder 8)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Wilmot Robertson, 1973 Apr (Box 139, Folder 9)
        - Incoming Correspondence - JP Lott (reprint), 1973 (Box 139, Folder 10)
        - Incoming Correspondence - WF Bennett, 1973 Apr 19 (Box 139, Folder 13)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Geo. Stephen Leonard (reprint), 1973 Apr 26 (Box 139, Folder 14)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Thank You's (reprint), 1973 Apr (Box 139, Folder 15)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Charles Stein, 1973 Apr 20 (Box 139, Folder 20)
        - Incoming Correspondence - AC Olshen re Articles from Commentary Magazine (reprint), 1973 Apr (Box 139, Folder 21)
        - Incoming Correspondence (reprint) - Biljon Invitation, 1985 Sep 2 (Box 139, Folder 35)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Security Pacific National Bank Revocation of Trust, 1987 Jan 23 (Box 139, Folder 46)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Bernard Rimland, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 59)
        - Incoming Correspondence (reprint) - Robert Graham, 1985 Jul 15 (Box 139, Folder 62)
        - Incoming Correspondence - James Jondrow, 1988 Nov 14 (Box 143, Folder 40)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Michael Riordan & Emmy Shockley, 1996 Dec 3 (Box 143, Folder 70)
        - Correspondence - Curriculum Vitae Albert B. Kapstrom, 1989 May 4 (Box 144, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence - Pugwash Conferences, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
        - Clippings - New York Times, 1968 March 4-18 (Box 144, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence Packet - W Thornton Read, 1972 January 1 (Box 144, Folder 4)
        - Karl Loeffler, 1965-1966 (Box 144, Folder 5)
        - Commonwealth Club of California Correspondence (Requests for Shockley's Speeches), 1967 (Box 144, Folder 6)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Charles H. Henry regarding large dark spot effect, 1977 Jan 13 (Box 144, Folder 7)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Linn Winterbotham, Palo Alto Historical Association, 1964 April 22 (Box 144, Folder 8)
        - Travis Osborne Twins Study Data Packet (includes correspondence), 1988 Sept 12 (Box 144, Folder 9)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Richard Lynn, 1987 Nov 11 (Box 144, Folder 10)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Arthur Jensen, 1986 Dec 17 (Box 144, Folder 11)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Howard Frost III, 1975 Nov 9 (Box 144, Folder 12)
        - Polygraphs in Politics Press List (includes IBM magnetic cards), 1976 Aug 28 (Box 144, Folder 13)
        - Outgoing Correspondence Packet - L.L. Heston re "on the 7-curve and Lykken Figures, 1987 Jun 23 (Box 144, Folder 14)
        - Behavior Genetics Association Information Packet, 1987 June (Box 144, Folder 15)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Arthur Jensen, 1988 May 7 (Box 144, Folder 16)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Arthur Jensen, 1987 Feb 24 (Box 144, Folder 17)
        - Incoming Correspondence - Arthur Jensen Packet, 1987 Jan 21 (Box 144, Folder 18)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Arthur Jensen, 1987 March 4 (Box 144, Folder 19)
        - Incmoing Correspondence Packet from P.T. Lykken after telephone conversation on 1988 Apr 19, circa 1988 April (Box 144, Folder 20)
        - 1-300 Revision, "Truth-Concern-Death", 1971 Dec 18 (Box 144, Folder 21)
        - Draft, Response to "paranoid accusation" by American Psychological Association, circa 1971 Dec (Box 144, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence Packet - Arthur Jensen, 1981 Aug 24 (Box 144, Folder 23)
        - Incoming Correspondence Packet - Henry Turkel, 1965 Jan 15 (Box 144, Folder 24)
        - Clippings - Related to Gustavus Adolphus Talk, 1964 Nov - 1965 Mar (Box 144, Folder 25)
        - Clippings, 1966 Nov (Box 144, Folder 26)
        - Clippings, 1968 Jan 31 - Feb 9 (Box 144, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence Packet - Hyink, Doolittle, Garn, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence Packet - Robert Kuttner, 1971-1972 (Box 144, Folder 29)
      - Outgoing Correspondence
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Jack N. James, 1976 Aug 11 (Box 116, Folder 66)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Dr. Gardner, circa 1966 (Box 114, Folder 38)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Editor of New York Times, 1967 Dec 19 (Box 121, Folder 18)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Gill Ewing, 1971 Aug 4 (Box 121, Folder 40)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Carl Rowan, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 45)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Franklin Gilchrist, 1971 Nov 16-18 (Box 121, Folder 46)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Contributors (Template Copy), 1969 Jan 24 (Box 121, Folder 55)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - The Harvard Educational Review, 1969 Mar 17 (Box 121, Folder 66)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - John W. Gardner, 1966-1968 (Box 121, Folder 69)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Dr. Jan Mohr, 1969 Apr 9 (Box 121, Folder 70)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Emmy Shockley to Stanford University Medical Staff, 1989 Jul 11 (Box 123, Folder 3)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Prof. Harry Munsinger, 1976 Sep 5 (Box 123, Folder 12)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Jack N. James, 1976 Aug 11-18 (Box 124, Folder 8)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Lee M. Hunt, 1976 Aug 27 (Box 124, Folder 10)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Response to News Articles (Pt. 1) from Shockley, 1973-1976 (Box 124, Folder 18)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Response to News Articles (Pt. 2) from Shockley, 1973-1976 (Box 124, Folder 19)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Glenn Dassoff, 1975 Nov (Box 124, Folder 40)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - "J", 1974 (Box 124, Folder 50)
        - 60 Minutes Letter to the Editor - W=S on Percy William Beridgeman Suicide, 1989 Apr 19 (Box 123, Folder 30)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Emmy to Hana and Ikue, 2000 Jan 6 (Box 129, Folder 22)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Various Drafts to Professor Peter H. Schonemann regarding "Who-stuck-who-first?", 1988 Mar 21 - May 5 (Box 130, Folder 13)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - AJ Torsiglieri, 1988 Apr 22 (Box 130, Folder 17)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Steven Harnad, 1986 Dec 20 (Box 130, Folder 19)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Candidate in the Republican Primary for the US Senate, 1982 Apr 12 (Box 137, Folder 5)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Gibbons & El Hoshay, 1968 May 13 (Box 137, Folder 14)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Emmy Shockley, 1988 Apr (Box 138, Folder 10)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - from Emmy Shockley, 1995-2000 (Box 138, Folder 14)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Philip Abelson, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 17)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Mrs. & Mr. RT Kendall (Box 138, Folder 46)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - T Edward Reed Jr. (draft) (Box 138, Folder 47)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - AF Coombes re Eugeneics Manuscript, 1973 May 4 (Box 138, Folder 82)
        - Outgoing Correspondence (reprint) - Ambassador Taswell, 1983 Dec 30 (Box 139, Folder 34)
        - Outgoing Correspondence (reprint) - Professor van Biljon, 1985 Dec 17 (Box 139, Folder 36)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Professor Louis va Biljon, 1986 Dec 31 (Box 139, Folder 37)
        - Outgoing Correspondence (reprint) - Harry Weyher and Hans Eysenck, 1986 Jun 22 (Box 139, Folder 40)
        - Correspondence - Drafts to Harry Musinger (Box 139, Folder 66)
        - Outgoing Correspondence - Steven Harnard, 1986 Dec (Box 143, Folder 19)
      - 1957-1978 (Box 56)
      - [includes Autograph requests, Alvarado corr. copies 1969-1974], 1979-1998 (Box 57)
      - [Includes correspondence between William Shockley and Linus Pauling regarding Ed Jackson] (Box 89, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence - Western Electric, 1973 Feb 9 (Box 111, Folder 11)
      - "The Planet is in peril: Nobel Laureates seek an answer", 1983 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence - Council Foundation 'For the Future of the Worlds' Children', 1989 Jul 14 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence - Consulate General of Sweden, 1990 Oct 18 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence - Nobelstiftelsen, 1987-1988 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence - University of Western Ontario Faculty, 1990 Oct 9 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence - Behavioral and Brain Sciences, 1988 Mar (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence - The Dong-A Daily Newspaper (Box 116, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence - David MacRae, 1988 Apr 28 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence - S. Mil'shtein, 1989 Jul 6 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence - KBOI News, 1967 Apr 14 (Box 116, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence - Curtis Gray, 1986 Nov 21 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence - William P. Herrell, 1992 Jun 30 (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - Column/Letter to Editor WSJ from W=S, 1986 Jul 14 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      - Telephone Conversation & Correspondence - Murray M. Silver, 1983-1986 (Box 116, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence - Careton Putnam, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 22)
      - University of Missouri-Rolla - Correspondence & Lecutures, 1983 Mar-Aug (Box 116, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence - Robert K. Graham & David W. Gore, 1989; email b/w the two gentlemen with the cc to William Shockley (Box 116, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence - Sri Chinmoy Silver Julbilee, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence - Modern Physics in America, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence - Olwin, Connelly, Chase, O'Donnell, & Weyher, 1980-1989 (Box 116, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence - C. Fredrick Bentley II, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence - International Academy of Science, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence - World Future Society, 1988 Aug 26 (Box 116, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence - JP Den Hartog, 1972-1981 (Box 116, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence - Robert Ardrey, 1969-1970 (Box 116, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence - Institute for Child Behavior Research, 1987 Dec (Box 116, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence - Gary S. Hahn, 1989 Apr 25 (Box 116, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence - United States Senate, 1969 Jul 17 (Box 116, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence - C. Northcote Parkinson, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence - Veterans Admin./ Medical Center, circa 1960s-1988 (Box 116, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence - Westvaco, 1987 Mar 24 (Box 116, Folder 43)
      - Corrrespondence - Dr. Moshe Goodman (Hewbrew Uni. of Jerusalem), 1988 Apr 26 (Box 116, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence - George W. Commons, 1986 Dec 23; Correspondence, Map, & Notes (Box 116, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence - J. Philippe Rushton (Uni. of W. Ontario), 1987 Jul 6 (Box 116, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence - I. Drigogine (Solvay Institute), 1986 Oct 12 (Box 116, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence - World Congress Alternatives & Environment, 1986 Sep 16 (Box 116, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence - Ena Tracy (Box 116, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence - Seymour M. Kessler, 1974 Sep 2 (Box 116, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence - RT Kendall & Frank Rimmerman, 1976 Dec 3 (Box 116, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence - Austin Treadwell White Introductions, 1932 (Box 116, Folder 62)
        Letters written to William Shockley or to people about William Shockley by Austin Treadwell White from the Los Angeles Athletic Club.
      - Correspondence - Roger A. Freeman, 1969 Jan 13-20 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence - Black Students & Eugeneics, 1970 (Box 121, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence - Eugeneics, Old Union Sit-In, Petition to Senate, 1970 Apr-Jul (Box 121, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence - Charles H. Townes, 1970 (Box 121, Folder 33)
      - California Institute of Technology - Correspondence, 1969 Feb (Box 121, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence - Jet Propulsion Laboratory, 1976 Aug-Sep (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence - Norma Astwood, 1972-1974 (Box 124, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence - (JAH) John A. Hornbeck, 1976 (Box 124, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence - Pearon and Weyher re. Book, 1989 Jan 21 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence - South Africa, 1985-1986 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence - Herbert Solomon, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 27)
      - Dempster #2 & Correspondence - F Smith (reprint), 1973 Dec 19 (Box 138, Folder 39)
        From inside of an envelope labeled "Dempster #2 & F Smith 19 Dec 73". A mix of news articles and correspondence from F Smith.
      - X=WS - Mail to 28 Dec 73 (reprint), 1973 (Box 138, Folder 40)
        In an envelope labeled " X=WS Mail to 28 Dec 73" with various topics but mostly about eugeneics and FREED.
      - Correspondence - Misc., 1976 (Box 138, Folder 61)
      - Action Mail - Correspondence Misc., 1976-1977 (Box 138, Folder 62)
        In an envelope that had a note saying that the mail in the envelope needs to have a response soon.
      - Correspondence - Misc. on various topics, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 75)
        Had strips of paper sticking out of the correspondence stack and the correspondences appear to be from something kind of group together before being put into the box.
      - Correspondence - Leeds Paper (reprint), 1973 May 23 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence - AF Coombes, 1973 Apr-May (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence - Letters with News Articles (reprint) (Box 139, Folder 22)
      - W=S Xeroxes - Correspondences & Articles, 1973 May-Jun; Small individual envelopes made according to content & date with correspondence, articles, or both. (Box 139, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence - Charles Colson at White House re Laureate Statement, 1970 Jun 4 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence reprints - "Hidden Momentum", 1968 (Box 139, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence - "Hidden Momentum" (reprint), 1967 (Box 139, Folder 31)
      - Van Vleck -Reprints of Correspondences and Writings about "Hidden Momentum Forces", 1968-1969 (Box 139, Folder 32)
      - Griswold Response and Cover Letter, 1986 Jul 15 (Box 139, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence - Westvaco, 1986 May 18-20 (Box 139, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence - Ikue and Hana Watanabe, 1997 Nov-Dec (Box 139, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence - Emmy Shockley & Harry Weyher, 1992 Sep
      - Correspondence - Harry Weyher & Hans Eysenck re Race, 1988 Nov (Box 143, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence - Senate Committee on Equal Opportunity, 1978 May 9 (Box 143, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence - Harry Weyher & Hiram Caton, 1992 Dec 1 (Box 143, Folder 65)
      - Correspondence - Harry Weyher & Emmy Shockley, 1994 Nov (Box 143, Folder 69)
    - correspondence, packets
      Found in packet envelopes, contents includes original incoming and outgoing correspondence, reprints of correspondences, pamphlets, books, etc. on various subjects and people.
      - Monograph - John Leohlin, Gardner Lindsey, & JN Spuhler (1 of 2), 1973 Jun-Nov (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Monograph - John Leohlin, Gardner Lindsey, & JN Spuhler (2 of 2), 1973 Jun-Nov (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence Packet - RT Osborne, 1973 Sep-Oct (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence Packet - Florida Education - Donald E. Buck, Maria G. Pitner, 1986-1987 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence Packet - Texas Instruments Consultation, 1974 Apr (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence Packet - Arthur Jensen, 1987 Jun (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence Packet - Dr. Shockley's Shocker, circa 1974 Apr (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence Packet - Council for Inter-America Security-Nicaraguan Freedom Fighters, circa 1982 (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence Packet - Informart Third Anniversary and Half of Fame, 1988 Feb (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence Packet - "A Theory of Human Population Differences", J Philippe Rushton, 1987 Jul 3 (Box 134, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence Packet - South Africa, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 134, Folder 11)
        Contents includes: "Soapy Water and Cabinda", "The Mankind Quarterly", "The HNP in the Present South Africa Political Situation", "The Role of the Temporal Lobe in Morphogenesis and Laterality of the Human Brain", "Where Have All the Children Gone?: A Survey on Family Planning in South Africa, and "IQ and the Nature-Nurture Controversy".
      - Correspondence Packets - NAS, Davis Resolution, 1971 Apr 27 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence Packet - NAS, Appeals Packet, 1971 Mar-Jun (Box 134, Folder 13)
        Reprints of correspondences regarding appeals to NAS (National Academy of Science). See also NAS